DAVID BUI

Buena Park, CA 90621 • Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/david-bui12/

• Phone: 408-600-5260 • Email: <u>buidavid.ol13703@gmail.com</u>

Summary:

Energetic customer service professional with 6+ years of related work experience. Passionate, motivated, and committed about building strong customer relationships, driving brand loyalty, and excited to deliver goals designed to increase customer engagement to ensure that the company provides excellent customer service and satisfaction that will meet both of the needs of the client and business. in bringing innovation and collaboration to the team. My true passion is for over the next few years I would like to take on more managerial responsibilities and potentially even take lead on some projects.

Skills:

Clear Communication Skills, Self Control, Taking Responsibility, Patience, Effective Listening, Attentiveness, Thick Skin, Customer Service, Teamwork, Leadership, Management Skills, Problem-solving, Critical Thinking, Adaptability, Organization, Time Management, Transferable Skills, Willingness to Learn/Improve.

Technical Skills:

Analysis, Microsoft Office, Email, Google Drive, Spreadsheet, Computer Skills, Troubleshooting

Work Experience:

Cisco - Networking, Cloud and Cybersecurity Solutions

Network Analyst

February 2021 - March 2021

Data Analysis of Cisco's DNA Center TAC cases

- Analyze TAC cases opened on DNA Center, in order to identify if we see any type of pain trends that Cisco should address first.
- Looking at 10K TAC Cases from last year from the current UI and identifying which features need to improve appropriate
 areas in future.
- Consult and assist with the internal department senior-level challenges.

Private Estate

On-Site Assistant Property Manager

March 2020 -

Assists in managing all aspects of a building's occupancy and maintenance.

 Meets with prospective tenants to show properties, conduct interviews, receive rental applications and explain terms of occupancy. Processes applications and conducts credit checks.

Accenture, Facebook Employee (Off Site)

Content Review Analyst

October 2017 - February 2020

Review and analyze a target number of content based on a set of internal policy guidelines.

- Investigated and resolved issues that are reported on clients' sites such as requests for account support and reports of
 potentially abusive content while maintaining a strong consistent 98 percent accuracy base.
- Actively analyzing and monitoring various digital platforms to identify potentially inappropriate usage including words, phrases, statements, videos, and images
- Perform review and help provide feedback on the process of technology and tools, and to provide an in-depth understanding of the different processes they are overseeing and understand to help the software engineers make better and wider use of existing knowledge.

YesVideo

Video Service Technician

October 2016 - January 2017

Responsible for setting up, installing, operating, testing, and troubleshooting video equipment.

- Performed electronic repairs, diagnosed errors or technical problems, ensure the equipment is installed according to designated layout and work properly.
- Exceeded hiring manager's expected requirement. Went above my duties as a contractor, reducing the time spent on inventory by 50%. Resulting in employee 100% satisfaction rating and recognition by the hiring manager.

Education:

Cybersecurity Certificate: UC Berkeley Extension — Berkeley, CA

24-week long intensive boot camp in Cybersecurity. Learn from skilled instructors and gain real-world
experience by collaborating with peers through hands-on application training in defensive and offensive
cybersecurity, networking, systems, web technologies, and databases.

BA in Radio, Television and Film: SAN JOSE STATE UNIVERSITY— San Jose, CA